It's been extremely difficult to report on the ground.
And for a long time, I was afraid to go to Portland
because I knew that the only people who would have my back,
like Julio said, were one of my friends on the ground
because there is no police force there.
I was terrified to go because I knew if I got shot or stabbed,
and I have been assaulted, I've been
mobbed and robbed in Austin, Texas by Antifa,
that nobody would come to help me.
So my plea to the entire administration,
especially to the DOJ, is every single radical left winger
who is in front of the ICE facility in Chicago,
in New York, in Portland, please make sure
that you use the full force of the law
to come after each and every single one of them
because it is us being soft on left wing violence that
has fomented all of the terror that we
have seen in this country.
And it is the left wing getting away time and time
again with assaulting law abiding American citizens that
has led us to this place.
So truly, to the Americans that I speak to on the ground,
they feel completely abandoned by their state and local
government.
So please step in.
We have Americans begging for the National Guard.
And to the media over here, please report on the truth.
Please do your jobs.
I'm an American citizen.
Everybody at this table simply views ourselves
as American citizens who have an iPhone and the will
to actually tell the truth.
So please take your job seriously and tell the truth
to the American people.
And thank you for letting me be here on behalf of Charlie
to continue his legacy of cleaning up the country.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Wow, you feel very strongly, I can see.
I'm mad.
I got beat up so many times, Mr. President.
My friends have gotten beaten up.
And I want to cry right now from happiness
because we have been completely ignored for so long.
For almost 10 years, we've been getting
assaulted on the streets.
I have watched children cry as their parents have
been attacked on the streets.
That should not be happening at our nation's capital.
So please, again, the DOJ, please
utilize the full force and go after each and every single one
of these people.
Fantastic.
Thank you very much.
Great, great job.
Impassioned.
That's important because you should feel like that.
Please, go ahead.
Mr. President, thank you for having us here
and bringing together this panel of brave, brave journalists,
everybody on this side of the room.
And no one can speak to the violence
better than these people here.
So I think we know that this is not just
a story about violence and chaos,
as you alluded to, Mr. President.
This is a money story.
And at the Government Accountability Institute,
my colleague and I, Peter Schweitzer and my eye
and our team, we followed the money.
And we followed it to the top of what
we call the protest industrial complex, Riot Inc.
And we found a network of NGOs.
It's not just the Soros Network, the Open Society Network.
It's other funding networks, the Arabella Funding Network,
the Tides Funding Network, Neville Roy
Singham and his network, Foreign Cash.
And it's also big left-wing funders.
Some of them are not citizens of this country.
Mr. Hansjörg Wyss of Switzerland.
They're pouring money into this entire ecosystem.
And so I want to share three money facts with you
about what we call Riot Inc.
Number one, like any corporation,
Riot Inc. has many divisions.
It doesn't just have the Antifa boots on the ground division.
It has PR divisions.
It has marketing divisions.
It has a very well-funded legal division
to get these boots on the ground back on the streets
as quickly as possible.
But it does have those investors that I mentioned.
Number two, we have identified dozens
of radical organizations, not just
the decentralized Antifa organizations,
but dozens of radical organizations
that have received more than $100 million
from the Riot Inc. investors.
These would be the lawyer groups.
These would be the groups that advocate
for calling good, honest Americans fascists, et cetera.
And then three, I think the most shocking thing
is that we have found that more than $100 million
in US taxpayer funding has flowed into these funding
networks, including at least $4 million
to these very groups themselves, not just Antifa types.
But there was an event in Atlanta called Stop Cop City.
Over 60 rioters were charged with domestic terrorism.
These groups received money for that
from both the billionaire class as well as taxpayer money.
So one other thing, this money helps
fund the decentralized crowdfunding platforms.
These are ways that Antifa, the John Brown Gun Club of Elm
Fork, which had links to that attack on the ICE facility,
the Socialist Rifle Association.
And just because they don't have LLCs or EIN numbers
doesn't mean they can't get paid.
Some of these funding platforms, crowdfunding platforms,
are funded by this network that we call Riot Inc.
So again, I want to thank you for your leadership,
for the whole cabinet's leadership on this.
We're going to keep following the money.
And I appreciate everything you're doing, sir.
Do you know the name of any of the funders?
Do you know the names?
Because if you do, I'd like you to give them to Cash or Pam.
Absolutely.
Or Christy.
Yeah, we'll do that.
As soon as you can.
That's all of you.
Because you probably know the names.
After a certain period of time, you tend to find out.
But these are people that do not have good intentions.